So unfortunate to start here for BC.Game,
got to play a 4v5.
这开局太难受了，一上来就只能打 4v5。
I mean, statistically, right?
Like one third of the rounds you've played on Dust2,
你看从数据上说也是这样，在你们打过的 Dust2 回合里，
you start with the disadvantage of a tag down to 20 HP,
or at this time, a kill.
差不多有三分之一的回合，开局不是先被打到只剩 20 血，就是像这次一样直接掉人。
It's kind of brutal.
这真的太伤了。
Yeah, and now you've got one AWP, right?
At least this is s1mple's, and then pistols around it.
对，而且现在你们就这一把大狙。好歹这把 AWP 在 s1mple 手里，周围再配几把手枪。
So very likely to see the lead being taken here for Team Vitality.
所以这一分看起来很可能会被 Team Vitality 收下，顺势拿到领先。
Oh, they've stacked up at the B bomb site.
That's the correct read yet again.
他们这次在 B 包点重兵堆防了，而且又一次读对了。
ropz, apEX and flameZ. ZywOo's got utility to check out.
mezii's gonna be lurking over in middle.
这边是 ropz、apEX 和 flameZ。ZywOo 手里有道具可以先清点，mezii 则会在中路摸机会。
Because it's a save round, I don't think any attention is gonna get pulled. Senzu, electronic and s1mple
因为这是个 save 局，我觉得他们不会被轻易调动。Senzu、electronic 和 s1mple
are just gonna be happy to play the B bomb site and see what happens.
就准备死守这个 B 包点，看看会发生什么。
s1mple, lined away, strikes on flameZ. Five-Seven in.
s1mple 架好了，先打掉了 flameZ。57手枪 也跟着顶上来。
Oh, s1mple's got another one. Just apEX, and s1mple's cleaning up.
噢，s1mple 又拿一个。只剩 apEX 了，而 s1mple 还在继续收人。
So the AWP, back-to-back triples on that B bomb site.
这把 AWP 在 B 包点连续两回合都打出了三杀。
And finally, they've been able to make something of the s1mple AWP. Talk about a one-man army right now.
他们终于把 s1mple 这把大狙的价值彻底打出来了。现在这真就是一人扛一队。